MEAN Stack Developer

(91)-6383780816

babujrayp@gmail.com

Professional Summary:

- Web Experienced in MEAN stack developer for 4 years.
- Always does projects in updated versions of technologies.
- Both Individual and Team worker

Technical Skills

Web Development: JavaScript, Nodejs

Frameworks & Template: Bootstrap, Anguar, expressjs, angular material desgin

Database: Mongodb.

Site Deployment: AWS(S3,SQS,SNS,EC2,CLOUDFRONT,CLOUD

WATCH, APIGATEWAY)

Education:

B.E: COMPUTER SCIENCE [2012]

KCG COLLEGE OF TECHNOLOGY, ANNA UNIVERSITY CHENNAI

Professional Experience:

Rinteger Technologies, Bangalore

[July 2018 -

Current]

MEAN Stack Developer

Current Employer Project Summary:

E-commerce – Rinteger Technologies

Title: E-commerce B2C Web Application

Duration: July 2018 – Mar 2020 Role: MEAN Stack Developer

Responsibilities:

Develop B2C Web application for client

- Developing & implementing new modules on Angular, integrating payment method, shippment integration, product added
- Inventory management, Price management, Invoice Management, Cutomer Management
- Also added SSR for Customer UI

Technologies: JavaScript, Angular, Nodejs, expressjs,, mongodb

<u>CRM</u>

Title: **CRM Application**

Duration: Mar 2020 – Nov 2020 Role: MEAN Stack Developer

Responsibilities:

Develop CRM Web application for client

- · Developing & implementing new modules on Angular,
- Implement All type Contact to save DB
- Using Marketing Service to Sent Messages, SMS
- Integration SMS, Email third party

Technologies: JavaScript, Angular, Nodejs, expressjs, mongodb

Operation (Internal Project)

Title: **Operation**

Duration: Nov 2020 – Mar 2021 Role: MEAN Stack Developer

Responsibilities

- Developing & implementing new modules on Angular,
- Implement All type Contact to save DB
- Using Marketing Service to Sent Messages, SMS
- Integration SMS, Email third party
- Invoice management, finance management, material management

Technologies: JavaScript, Angular, Nodejs, expressjs, mongodb

E-commerce - Rinteger Technologies

Title: **B2B Web Application**

Duration: Mar 2021 - Present

Role: MEAN Stack Developer

Responsibilities:

Develop B2B Web application for client

- Developing & implementing new modules on Angular, integrating payment method, shippment integration
- Inventory management, Price management, Invoice Management, Cutomer Management, Catalogue Management
- · Also added SSR for Customer UI

Technologies: JavaScript, Angular, Nodejs, expressjs,, mongodb

PERSONAL DETAILS:

Date of Birth: 08 July 1991

Gender : Male

Marital Status: Single

Nationality : Indian

Father : M. Joseph

Address: Manvalakurichi, Vadakanpagam - 629252.

I hereby declare that all the facts provided above is true up to my knowledge.

PLACE:

DATE: (Yesu Babu J)